♪♪
♪ Do you know what's worth fighting for ♪
♪ When it's not worth dying for? ♪
♪ Does it take your breath away ♪
♪ And you feel yourself suffocating? ♪
♪ Does the pain weigh out the pride? ♪
♪ And you look for a place to hide? ♪
♪ Did someone break your heart inside? ♪
♪ You're in ruins ♪
♪ One, twenty one guns ♪
♪ Lay down your arms ♪
♪ Give up the fight ♪
♪ One, twenty one guns ♪
♪ Throw up your arms into the sky ♪
♪ You and I ♪
♪ When you're at the end of the road ♪
♪ And you lost all sense of control ♪
♪ And your thoughts have taken their toll ♪
♪ When your mind breaks the spirit of your soul ♪
♪ Your faith walks on broken glass ♪
♪ And the hangover doesn't pass ♪
♪ Nothing's ever built to last ♪
♪ You're in ruins ♪
♪ One, twenty one guns ♪
♪ Lay down your arms ♪
♪ Give up the fight ♪
♪ One, twenty one guns ♪
♪ Throw up your arms into the sky ♪
♪ You and I ♪
♪ Did you try to live on your own ♪
♪ When you burned down the house and home? ♪
♪ Did you stand too close to the fire? ♪
♪ Like a liar looking for forgiveness from a stone ♪
♪♪
♪ When it's time to live and let die ♪
♪ And you can't get another try ♪
♪ Something inside this heart has died ♪
♪ You're in ruins ♪
♪ One, twenty one guns ♪
♪ Lay down your arms ♪
♪ Give up the fight ♪
♪ One, twenty one guns ♪
♪ Throw up your arms into the sky ♪
♪ Lay down your arms ♪
♪ Give up the fight ♪
♪ One, twenty one guns ♪
♪ Throw up your arms into the sky ♪
♪ You and I ♪